Approximately, we have seen that this feature needs to be built.
It is not very complex.
But it can be very complex if they have added age.
No, we have a list of offers.
There is no complex at all.
Because AI means we don't actually use LLM.
Now, we are going to make a call
that we have all the offers.
You suggest top three optimizations
that the user can reach the best offer in the next few months to one year.
That's it. This is all it is.
But from the customer point of view,
should we show them that this is all AI driven?
No, no. Zero.
What we use in engineering is not a concern of the customer.
Why?
Because if we put a prompt,
the agent will answer.
I don't trust them.
It's not like that.
I don't think so.
In engineering, I don't think so.
Do we say that we use Postgres for backend?
No, but the recommendations are AI based.
AI is telling the recommendations.
Who cares? It is our recommendation engine.
But how do you do it?
The basis matters.
Because if AI is saying something
and the actual CA is saying something,
then people will trust the actual CA's information.
The actual CA is saying.
In engineering tools,
AI is just another engineering tool.
People have no concern about what engineering tool you are using.
But they trust the answer that they are giving.
They trust us.
How?
We will have to tell them something.
Before AI, the actual recommendation engines existed.
Netflix doesn't recommend it.
We think you will like this.
Did you watch one video?
Yes, I did.
Where do they say that we use machine learning algorithms?
Or do we use that?
The good companies don't say that we use AI.
They focus on the good ones.
We tell them that we use AI.
We use it.
Shut up, shut up.
You are an AI driven company in engineering.
On the contrary, I have lost my trust.
You said you are a CA driven company.
But would I have trusted you?
Who says that? Amazon?
There is only one problem.
where intelligence is shown,
we are shown that
basically it is a product.
Nothing is AI.
We never mention AI.
Google shows the flights.
They show the flights that these prices are low.
I am looking for a ticket to Bangalore.
How do I look for a ticket?
You tell me how much will it cost if I go to Bangalore from Chennai?
How much will it cost if I go to Bangalore from Coimbatore?
How much will it cost if I go to Mumbai from here?
I do all this.
They told me that these prices are low in Bangalore.
I have a lot of confidence.
Do you use AI?
Do you check the old data?
It is a good thing.
There is only one conflict.
What does Birbal do?
What does he learn?
Funding is basically given to AI companies.
It is not our competition.
Don't worry about it.
Birbal is a competitor.
Just for context.
I am also looking at the same point of view.
What does he do in the Indian market?
Is he very strong?
They call us.
Nowadays, tele-calling has become a lot of AI.
And there is a 95% chance
that in one or two sentences
we can't say that he is a human or an AI.
Such calls come these days.
Or we call them
and say that they are AI.
Where do they say that they are AI calls?
What do we use for engineering?
What is the customer's concern?
That guy is a fool.
That's why he is doing all this.
Basically, he gets funding
if he uses AI.
Nowadays, we don't even get funding
Nowadays, we don't even get funding.
Top 3 tips.
But they must be accurate.
Why are we seeing this?
You don't have a salary.
Salary...
We are not seeing a gap between two offers.
They are accurate.
No one can say that they are AI.
We are not going to get beaten up.
We are telling them
your offer is this.
The closest offer.
This feature is like
if someone says
you are giving so much money
they are like
how can you be so helpful?
It's okay bro.
In the beginning,
we used to think
that people don't believe
that we don't get any income
from the bank.
Where do you get income from?
You must be a big company.
But it's not like that.
We designed it.
We arranged the communication.
We said we are poor.
We are just two kids
working in the basement.
It's absolutely no problem.
As long as our testimonials are strong.
We launched it for the first time.
We posted it on reddit.
Guys, please evaluate my idea.
And if someone comes with a good intent
we have to appreciate them.
And if someone says
please come and see my loan process.
And if we genuinely satisfy them
we don't have to worry
that it was good.
There is nothing to worry about.
As long as
every customer is genuinely satisfied
we don't care how the mass market
looks at us.
how the next customer looks at us.
That's all we have to focus on.
We just have to climb the ladder of the customer.
Don't launch a mass
and bring a mass funnel to us.
We don't care what the mass perception is.
We just care about the next customer's perception.
And as a satisfied customer
as a chief product
I will take care of this.
What will I do?
I will talk to every customer personally.
I will ensure that
they should be satisfied.
There are many people
who want to
take their surveys
and give them a gift card.
And the one we like